bigsmudge.com 2010-01-06

# Privacy Policy | Big Smudge - Humor, Babes and Headkicks

Bigsmudge.com will always protect its user’s privacy. Our Privacy Policy is outlined below. Thank you.

**Internet User Information**

On Big Smudge, when you click on an ad, your personal identity and information, such as: Name, Telephone Number, Address, and E-Mail address will not be collected or stored. Certain information that cannot identify any user, such as Internet Service Provider and Browser type, may be used. It is common practice, and this type of information falls under the non-personal identity information.

There may be instances when you may wish to voluntarily provide your personal information to a specific type of ad, such as a purchase order form, or questionnaire. Bigsmudge.com will not collect or store any information, and a third party is usually responsible for the collection.

Bigsmudge.com will not release any information from users who contact and communicate with any personnel from bigsmudge.com.

Bigsmudge.com will never sell any of your information. We will not release any data that identifies you personally as a user.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
Bigsmudge.com uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number)via the DART cookie, about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)  

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)  

**BE SAFE AND PROTECT YOURSELF ONLINE**

Despite our best efforts, the best thing you as a user can do is to protect yourself from instances where your identity can be revealed. The internet is full of advertisers, hackers, and software programs that want to secure your information. Common sense can help prevent many cases of personal information release. While on the internet, please consider your source before relinquishing any information.

**Insecure forms of online communication:**

\- E-Mail (Often an insecure form of communication. Third Parties can intercept unencrypted content sent via email. Chat rooms, bulletin systems and other forms of electronic communication can subject you to the dreaded spam. Only provide your e-mail if you feel that it is safe to do so. Use your discretion.

Don’t fall for any scams where an unknown source is requesting your personal information. Do not disclose your Name, Password, Credit Card information, Address, or any other information related to your person.

**If you have any other questions regarding our Privacy Policy, don’t hesitate to contact us**

We here at Bigsmudge.com value your time spent on our site, and would not provide any information to anyone, for any reason. If you have any more questions regarding our Privacy Policy, or if there is anything you are unsure about, contact us at

Thank you, 

Big Smudge
